<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A career That&#39;s Real on Blogophonic</title>
    <link>https://truelinker.github.io/MyungBlog/career/</link>
    <description>Recent content in A career That&#39;s Real on Blogophonic</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 09:31:27 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://truelinker.github.io/MyungBlog/career/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PCIe Device Driver</title>
      <link>https://truelinker.github.io/MyungBlog/career/pciedevicedriver/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://truelinker.github.io/MyungBlog/career/pciedevicedriver/</guid>
      <description>Participated in the SSHDD development. A small-capacity SSD inside the HDD is a drive connected by a PCIe bus. So, frequently read data is stored on the SSD, so it is a drive with improved speed compared to the existing HDD. My part is PCIe AHCI drive driver development, because the SSD was used AHCI connected through PCIe bus.
Steps for implment the PCIe AHCI device driver Assume the PCIe End point(EP) address is hardcorded to 0x10000.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secure Drive</title>
      <link>https://truelinker.github.io/MyungBlog/career/secure-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://truelinker.github.io/MyungBlog/career/secure-drive/</guid>
      <description>Now I&amp;rsquo;m working at Western Digital as a firmware developer on a team that provides a common security engine for SSDs and HDDs. I am in charge of developing Security APIs so that the security engine provided by the team can be used according to the HDD characteristics. TCG protocols (TCG enterprise, opal, pyrite, etc). Sanitize ATA Security 1. [TCG] (https://nvmexpress.org/wp-content/uploads/TCGandNVMe_Joint_White_Paper-TCG_Storage_Opal_and_NVMe_FINAL.pdf) provides that data stored on HDDs or SSDs is self-encrypted under policy-based access control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serial communication</title>
      <link>https://truelinker.github.io/MyungBlog/career/sio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://truelinker.github.io/MyungBlog/career/sio/</guid>
      <description>I developed a serial communication protocol. As for the background, as the tester that uses only a single serial bus was newly introduced, I had to change the firmware to use it with the tester that uses the existing dual serial bus, and I was in charge of developing the fimrware. The purpose of this project is to change the firmware to work with testers with different serial communication methods on the same firmware.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SMR</title>
      <link>https://truelinker.github.io/MyungBlog/career/smr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://truelinker.github.io/MyungBlog/career/smr/</guid>
      <description>Participated in the drive managed SMR HDD development. Because the size of Read Header in HDD is smaller than Write Header, it is possible to write more densely when writing. This is the basic concept of SMR (Shingled Magnetic Recording). There are two main types of SMR HDDs: Host Managed SMR and Drive Managed SMR. The reason for dividing into two is that for SMR drives capable of only sequential write/read, the location of LBA and actual physical location is different each time it is written, so an indirection mapping table is needed for this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Built-in Contact Form</title>
      <link>https://truelinker.github.io/MyungBlog/career/built-in-contact-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://truelinker.github.io/MyungBlog/career/built-in-contact-form/</guid>
      <description>Formspree makes it easy to receive submissions from HTML forms on your static website. Functional Form This theme has a form-to-email feature built in, thanks to the simple Formspree integration. All you need to activate the form is a valid recipient email address saved in the front matter of the form (/content/forms/contact.md). Of course, the example shown below (your@email.here) must not be used. Please use your actual email address.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
