<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A portfolio That&#39;s Real on Blogophonic</title>
    <link>https://truelinker.github.io/MyungBlog/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in A portfolio That&#39;s Real on Blogophonic</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 09:31:27 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://truelinker.github.io/MyungBlog/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Log Parser</title>
      <link>https://truelinker.github.io/MyungBlog/portfolio/logparser/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://truelinker.github.io/MyungBlog/portfolio/logparser/</guid>
      <description>Log Parser In order to solve numerous bugs and problems, I need to look at log data generated by many drives. However, sometimes the log amount exceeds several hundred megabytes. In order to save time and effort, I created a parser python script, which is helping me to solve more problems in a timely manner while reducing time and effort. How it works [1] Enter the path of the file where the Enum values are defined.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web RTC</title>
      <link>https://truelinker.github.io/MyungBlog/portfolio/webrtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://truelinker.github.io/MyungBlog/portfolio/webrtc/</guid>
      <description>Web RTC Using the WebRTC open source, I&amp;rsquo;d modified to implment my own p2p video chat application between the android native app and chrom web app.
Github : https://github.com/truelinker/webrtc_p2pvideo
How it works Two peers (Android application and web application) connect to a room created by a server, I used a Javascript web server using node.js and exchange information such as each other&amp;rsquo;s network information (ip, port). When starting a video call, the call starts by exchanging each other&amp;rsquo;s media information based on the given network information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Word Memorization App</title>
      <link>https://truelinker.github.io/MyungBlog/portfolio/vocamaster/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://truelinker.github.io/MyungBlog/portfolio/vocamaster/</guid>
      <description>Voca Master This is an Android application that I developed in 2011. This is an application that helps you memorize new English words.
Github : https://github.com/truelinker/vocaMaster
Click the video demo above. ☝️ Abstraction Mobile devices are useful in many respects such as education, entertainment, and so on, because people bring their mobile gadgets all the time. Therefore, apps running on the devices are exposed to users anytime and anywhere. For the summer personal project, I‟ve developed an education app for the Android platform; the app is for helping people to memorize vocabularies with spending remnant time such as during waiting a bus, waiting a meal, and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
