<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Embedded Systems on Blogophonic</title>
    <link>https://truelinker.github.io/MyungBlog/tags/embedded-systems/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Embedded Systems on Blogophonic</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://truelinker.github.io/MyungBlog/tags/embedded-systems/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Flash Writer Implementation for Embedded Systems</title>
      <link>https://truelinker.github.io/MyungBlog/career/flashwriter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://truelinker.github.io/MyungBlog/career/flashwriter/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview Developed a sophisticated Flash Writer application for initializing flash memory in new embedded systems. This critical tool enables the programming of secondary boot loaders (SBL) and establishes the foundation for multi-core boot sequences.
Technical Architecture Boot Sequence Architecture The boot sequence follows a carefully orchestrated process, starting from ROM and progressing through multiple stages:
Figure 1: Complete boot sequence flow showing ROM, Flash Writer, and SBL stages
Flash Writer Operation Flow Initial Download Phase Figure 2: Flash Writer download and initialization sequence</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PCIe AHCI Device Driver Development</title>
      <link>https://truelinker.github.io/MyungBlog/career/pciedevicedriver/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://truelinker.github.io/MyungBlog/career/pciedevicedriver/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview Led the development of a PCIe AHCI device driver for a Solid State Hybrid Drive (SSHD) system. This innovative storage solution combines HDD capacity with SSD performance by utilizing a PCIe-connected SSD cache for frequently accessed data.
Technical Architecture System Overview The SSHD architecture integrates traditional HDD storage with a PCIe-connected SSD cache:
Figure 1: High-level architecture of the Hybrid Storage System
PCIe Port Initialization Flow The PCIe controller initialization follows a precise sequence to ensure reliable operation:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
